大伙们 你们一定不会相信
Hey, hey! Guys, you won't believe this!
- 我刚刚跟我的经纪人谈过…   - 我的天啊
- I just got off the phone with my agent...     - Oh, my God!
- 对不起 太快了 你说吧   - 好吧
- I'm sorry. Too soon. You go.     - Okay.
我因为《我们的日子》被提名
I got nominated for my part on Days of Our Lives!
- 喔 乔伊 这真的是太好了    - 恭喜你
- Oh, Joey, good for you!     - Congratulations!
- 我不敢相信你获得艾美奖提名    - 不是
- I can't believe you're nominated for an Emmy!     - No, no.
- 肥皂剧文摘奖？ - 不 我被提名"肥皂奖"
- Soap Opera Digest Award?     - Nope, I'm up for a "Soapie."
甜心 那是你乱编的吗？
Honey, is that something you're making up?
不 那是真的 这个奖从1998年开始颁发
No, no, no, it's real! And it has been since 1998.
嘿 瑞秋 我被提名肥皂奖了
Hey, Rach, Rach. I'm up for a Soapie!
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
天啊 那是排名第三的肥皂剧大奖
Oh, my God! That is the third most prestigious soap opera award there is!
谢谢 我猜我们知道 我该带谁参加颁奖典礼
Thank you! Well, I guess now we know who I'm taking to the awards.
别跟我开这种玩笑  所有明星都会去吗？
Oh, stop that! Don't kid about that! Will all the stars be there?
很多人都说他们会去
Many are scheduled to appear.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
- 我不能去 我一定会太紧张   - 那就换我去吧
- Oh, my God. I can't go. I'll be too nervous!     - Okay, I'll go.
不行 你要结婚了 这个机会是我的
No! You are getting married. This is all I have.
恩斯特穆伯拉特假设 迅猛龙受到威胁时…
And Ernest Muhlbrat first hypothesized that the velociraptor, when threatened...
他会把颈部肌肉张开 发出尖锐的叫声…
...would expand its collar and emit a high-pitched noise...
将敌人吓跑
...to frighten off its predator.
路易斯 什么事？
Yes, Mr. Lewis?
他是怎么叫的？
What kind of noise?
他会发出尖锐吵杂的声音
Just a high-pitched, intimidating noise.
那到底是什么样子？
But like how?
我们并不确定
Well, we... We don't know for sure.
但我想 应该是这样的…
But in my head, it sounded something like this, uh:
当然 这只是种猜测
Of course, this is just conjecture.
好了 今天的课上到这里
Ahem, okay. That's, uh... That's all for today.
摩斯先生 我能跟你谈谈吗？
Mr. Morse, can I see you for a moment?
什么事？教授
Yes, sir?
我得跟你谈谈你的期中考成绩
Mr. Morse, I need to talk to you about your midterm exam.
- 恐怕我得把你当掉   - 为什么？
- I'm afraid I had to fail you.     - Why?
你得答对百分之六十才能过关
Well, you need 60 percent to pass.
- 我的分数是多少？ - 七分
- What'd I get?     - Seven.
那不是很好
That's not so good.
不 那糟透了 奈德 到底发生了什么事？
No, no, it's not. What happened there, Ned?
或许你可以放我一马 我恋爱了
Well, maybe you can cut me some slack. I'm sort of in love.
抱歉 但那真的不是我的问题
I'm sorry, but that's really not my problem.
我爱上了你
I'm in love with you.
那好像跟我有一点关系
Well, that brings me in the loop a little.
所以我才会考那么烂 我没办法专心上课
See, that's why I did so bad on this test. I'm having a hard time concentrating.
你站在讲台上讲课的时候…
When you're up there and you're teaching...
表情是那么地严肃…
...and your face gets all serious...
你看起来好帅 当你穿着紧身套头毛衣时…
...you look so good. When you wear that tight little turtleneck sweater...
好了
Okay. Ned, um...
我是你的老师 对不起
I, uh... Ha, ha. I'm your teacher. I'm sorry.
你是学生
You're... You're a student.
而且我喜欢女人
And I... And I like women, ha, ha.
虽然有人在椅背上写了一些话
In spite of what may be written on the backs of some of these chairs.
天啊
Oh, my God.
吧台那个男人在看你
That guy at the counter is totally checking you out.
真的吗？
Really?
- 我的天啊 他真的好帅    - 去吧
- Oh, my God, he's really cute.     - Heh. Go for it.
菲比 我订婚了
Phoebe, I'm engaged.
我建议你去问他的 电话号码 以防万一
I'm just saying, get his number, just in case.
说不定钱德发生意外 丧失了性能力…
But if Chandler is in an accident and can't perform sexually, you know...
他要你找个爱人 满足他无法满足你的那部分
...then he would want you to take a lover to satisfy the needs he can no longer fulfill.
- 嗨   - 喔
- Hi. I...     - Oh.
我能跟你说句话吗？
Can I just tell you something? Um...
我真的受宠若惊 但我订婚了
I'm very flattered, but, uh, I'm engaged. Ha, ha.
哇哦 额… 这真的是有点难堪
Wow, uh... This is kind of embarrassing.
事实上 我想跟你朋友说话
I was actually coming over to talk to your friend.
你应该觉得难堪
Well, you should be embarrassed.
- 我以为你知道我在看你   - 我知道 但那真的很好玩
- I thought you knew I was looking at you.     - I did, but that was really fun.
"得奖的是…乔伊崔比亚尼"
"The winner is Joey Tribbiani!"
"哇
"Oh, wow.
我真的没想到我会得奖…
I honestly never expected this. I, uh...
我没有准备演讲稿…
I didn't prepare a speech.
我要谢谢我的父母 他们一直支持着我…
But I'd like to thank my parents, who've always been there for me.
我还要谢谢我的朋友 钱德 摩妮卡 菲比 瑞秋…"
Also like to thank my friends, Chandler, Monica, Phoebe, Rachel..."
- 我排在第四名？ - 天啊
- I'm fourth?     - Jeez!
看看你 拿着你的枫糖奖
Look at you with your little maple syrup award!
拜托你不要告诉别人这件事
Maybe you don't tell anyone about this.
什么？别
What? No.
那没有什么大不了的 我也会拿着洗发精的瓶子那么做
It's not a big deal. I do that too, with my shampoo bottle.
- 真的吗？ - 没错
- Really?     - Yeah.
- 你假装自己得了什么奖？ - 葛莱美奖
- What award are you practicing for?     - Grammy.
- 我是最佳新进艺人  - 哦
- Best New Artist.     - Ooh.
肥皂奖的人今天打电话给我 我还得上台颁奖
Oh, hey, listen. The Soapies people called today. I also get to present an award.
- 哇 真是太好了   - 耶
- Aw, that's great.     - Yeah.
好耶 所以就算你没得奖你也有机会上台
So you'll get on stage even if you don't win.
- 你认为我不会得奖？ - 你当然会得奖
- You... You don't think I'm gonna win?     - Of course I do.
哦
Oh.
但最受欢迎死而后生奖？ 那个奖的竞争很激烈
But, you know, Favorite Returning Character is a tough category, Joey.
你要跟一个火葬了之后 还能活过来的人竞争
I mean, you're up against the guy who survived his own cremation.
不 我知道或许我不会得奖 只是…
Yeah. No, I know I might not win. But it's just...
我从来没有被提名过 我真的很想得奖
I've never even been nominated before. I want it so much.
或许你会得奖
Well, and you'll probably get it.
但你应该开始练习 你的"运动家精神"表情
But you should probably start practicing your "gracious-loser" face.
当摄影机拍到你时 你得表现出失望的样子
Like, when the cameras are on you and you wanna look disappointed...
但也得表现出对方是 实至名归的表情 就像这样…
...but also that your colleague deserved to win. Sort of like:
- 嘿   - 你知道吗？
- Hey.     - You know?
- 你也假装自己没得到葛莱美奖？ - 不 我是葛莱美奖的常胜军
- You practice losing at the Grammys too?     - Oh, no, at the Grammys, I always win.
啊
Ah.
- 理    - 嘿 你跟杰克约会还顺利吗？
- Oh, hey.     - Hey. How'd your date go with Jake?
太棒了 我们一直注视着彼此
Great. We couldn't keep our eyes off each other all night.
每隔一阵子他就会靠过来 摸我的头发跟脖子
Then every once in a while, he'd lean over and stroke my hair, and then touch my neck.
住手 菲比 你害得我好痒
Okay, stop it. You're getting me all tingly.
我只能想着 他要吻我了吗…？
All I could think of was, "Is he gonna kiss me? Is he?"
- 他吻了你吗？ - 我是个淑女 绝不会泄露那种事
- And did he?     - I'm a lady, Monica. I don't kiss and tell.
但这个吻痕说明了一切
But this hickey speaks for itself.
好了 我知道了
Okay, okay, I got it. I got it.
我真的好喜欢他 感觉上像是我今天喝了十杯酒
I just like him so much that I just feel like I've had 10 drinks today.
而我只喝了六杯
And I've only had six.
我第一次跟钱德约会后 再也没有那样的感觉
Oh. You know, I haven't had that feeling since I first starting going out with Chandler.
- 我永远都不会再有那样的感觉了   - 你的口气跟男人一模一样
- Wow, I'm never gonna have that feeling again.     - You sound like a guy.
不 男人会说 "我永远 都不能再跟别人上床了"
Heh. No, a guy would say, "I'm never gonna get to sleep with anyone else." Heh.
我永远都不能再跟别人上床了
Oh, my God. I'm never gonna sleep with anyone else!
我一直忙着筹备婚礼 完全忘了我要放弃什么
I've been so busy planning the wedding, I forgot about all the things I'd be giving up.
我再也不会有初吻
I mean, I'm never gonna have a first kiss again.
你会有最后的吻别
You'll have a last kiss.
我能问你一件事吗？ 有男人喜欢过你吗？
Can I ask you something? You ever had a guy have a crush on you?
那就是你要帮我打领带的原因？
Is that why you wanted to tie my tie?
我班上的学生说他爱上我了
There's this kid in my class who said he's in love with me.
- 哇   - 耶
- Whoa!     - Yeah.
- 哇什么？ - 罗斯有男朋友了
- Whoa, what?     - Ross has a boyfriend.
我没有男朋友
I do... I do not have a boyfriend.
我班上有个男学生暗恋我
There's a guy in one of my classes who has a crush on me.
- 真的吗？ - 对 我不知道
- Really?     - Yeah. I don't know.
去年是伊莉莎白 现在是这个孩子…
I mean, last year, Elizabeth, now this kid...
这是怎么一回事？我散发出…
What... What... What is it? Am I giving out some kind of...
性感教授的气质吗？
...a sexy-professor vibe?
现在看起来不像
Not right now.
重点是我的天生丽质 让他期中考被当掉
The point is, my natural charisma has made him fail his midterm.
我为那个孩子感到难过
Aw, see now I feel bad for the kid.
我也曾经暗恋过老师 那真的很难受
I had a crush on a teacher once, and it was so hard, you know.
我没办法专心上课 每次他看着我时 我都会脸红
I couldn't concentrate and I blushed every time he looked at me.
你还记得十九岁时的恋爱滋味吧
Come on, you remember what it's like to be 19 and in love.
- 我是可以放他一马   - 太棒了
- Yeah, guess I can cut him some slack.     - Yeah.
- 你怎么忘记那个老师的？ - 我没有
- How'd you get over that teacher?     - I didn't.
我跟他上床了
I got under him.
问题解决了
Problem solved.
- 再见 菲比   - 好的 再见
- Bye, Phoebe.      - Okay, bye.
- 好的 再见   - 再见
- All right. Bye.     - Bye.
我们在门边说再见 不想炫耀我们的新恋情
We said goodbye at the door so as not to flaunt our new love.
菲比 没关系 你不必顾虑到我
Phoebe, it's okay. You don't have to tiptoe around me.
我已经想过了 你知道吗？
I've been thinking about it, and um... You know what?
我可以接受没有心动感觉的生活
I'm okay about not having that new-relationship feeling.
- 我已经开始想你了  - 我也会想你
- I miss you already!     - I miss you too!
那真的太棒了 但我不会拿我的幸福跟你交换
See, that's what I mean. That's great, but I wouldn't trade in what I have for that.
我会一辈子跟钱德相守
I mean, I'm gonna be with Chandler for the rest of my life.
- 那让我觉得幸福   - 恩
- That's what makes me happy.     - Mm-hm.
快坐下 我们正在谈 我们的关系有多深厚…
Hey, sweetie, come here, sit down. We were talking about how our relationship is...
是那么地有意义 真的是那样 你觉得呢？
...deep and meaningful. It really is, don't you think?
喔 一点都没错
Oh, totally.
拉一下我的手指
Pull my finger.
最受欢迎死而复生男演员…
Presenting the award for Favorite Returning Male...
轮到我了
This is it. This is my category!
- 你的演讲稿带了吗？ - 带了
- Got your speech?     - Got my speech.
- 运动家精神表情练习好了吗？ - 有
- Got your gracious-loser face?     - Yep.
记住 如果你得奖了 你得抱我
Now, Joey, remember, if you win, you have to hug me.
好 我能捏你的屁股吗？
Okay. Can I squeeze your ass?
- 在电视上吗？ - 是啊
- On TV?    - Yeah.
- 可以   - 好吧
- Yeah.     - Okay.
在最受欢迎死而复生 男演员奖方面被提名的有
In the category of Favorite Returning Male Character, the nominees are:
约翰惠勒 《综合医院》
John Wheeler from General Hospital.
盖文葛拉罕 《年少轻狂》
Gavin Graham from The Young and the Restless.
唐肯哈灵顿 《热情》
Duncan Harrington from Passions.
乔伊崔比亚尼 《我们的日子》
And Joey Tribbiani from Days of Our Lives.
得奖的是
And the Soapie goes to:
盖文葛拉罕 《年少轻狂》
Gavin Graham from The Young and the Restless.
颁发最受欢迎女配角奖的是
Presenting the Favorite Supporting Actress award:
演《我们的日子》的乔伊崔比亚尼
Joey Tribbiani from Days of Our Lives.
所有在这个奖项 被提名的优秀女演员…
Any one of the brilliant actresses nominated for this award tonight...
得奖都是实至名归 可惜只有一个人能得奖
...deserves to take it home. Unfortunately, only one can.
最受欢迎女配角奖被提名的有
The nominees for Favorite Supporting Actress are:
《热情》 艾玲高菲
From Passions, Erin Goff.
《一生一次》 玛丽墨琳毕雪
From One Life to Live, Mary Lauren Bishop.
《我的孩子们》  莎拉蕾妮
From All My Children, Sarah Renee.
《我们的日子》 洁西卡艾许丽
And from Days of Our Lives, Jessica Ashley.
得奖的是
And the winner is:
洁西卡艾许丽 《我们的日子》
Jessica Ashley from Days of Our Lives.
很不幸 洁西卡今晚因故无法出席…
Uh, unfortunately, Jessica couldn't be with us tonight...
我要代表她接受这个奖
...so I'll be accepting this award on her behalf.
我相信洁西卡…
And I'm sure that Jessica...
会想谢谢我的父母…
...would like to thank my parents...
他们一直都很支持我
...who always believed in me.
她也感谢我的朋友
And she'd also like to thank my friends:
钱德 摩妮卡 罗斯 菲比跟瑞秋…
Chandler, Monica, Ross, Phoebe and Rachel...
她就坐在那边
...who's sitting right there.
乔伊 我们为什么要急着离开？
Joey, why did we have to rush out of there so fast?
我们得赶快离开 因为…
We had to get out of there because...
你看我拿了什么回家 哈哈
Look what I won! Ha-ha-ha.
我的天啊 你偷走她的奖杯
Oh, my God. You stole her award.
不…我代表她收下它
No, no, no. I'm accepting it on her behalf.
我想你不知道"代表"是什么意思
I don't think you know what "behalf" means.
我当然知道 它是个动词 意思是"我能分一半"
Sure I do. It's a verb. As in "I be half-in' it"!
乔伊
Joey...
- 你得把它还回去   - 为何？我应该得奖的 我好想得奖
- You have got to take this back.     - Why? I should've won one. I really wanted it.
她根本不在乎才没有出席 它也可以拿来当葛莱美
She didn't even care enough to come to the thing. It could also be a Grammy.
不 乔伊
No, Joey.
没有人看到我把它拿走 整个桌子上都是奖杯
Come on, Rach. No one saw me take it. There was a whole table full of them.
你想要一个不属于你的奖杯吗？
Do you really want an award that you didn't win?
不 我想要一个属于我的奖杯 但没有人愿意让我得奖
No, I want an award I did win. But nobody's given me any of those!
如果我把它摆在这里 大家就会看到它…
Plus, look, hey, Rach. If I put it up, when people come over, they'll see it...
以为我真的得奖了
...and they'll think I won it.
乔伊 上面写着"最佳女配角奖"
Joey, it says "Best Supporting Actress."
我可以把那个刮掉
I can scratch that right off.
乔伊 这样是不对的 你得把它还回去
Joey, no, this is wrong. You have to take it back.
你不会想这样把奖杯拿回家 你真的有演戏天分
Okay? You don't wanna win an award this way. You're very talented.
有一天你会真的得奖 那对你来说才有意义
And someday you're gonna win one of these for real and that one is gonna mean something.
- 好吧   - 好吗？谢谢
- Oh, all right.     - All right? Thank you.
- 我明天就把它还回去   - 谢谢
- I'll take it back tomorrow.     - Thank you.
- 如果我不能拥有它 你也不能拥有它   - 啊
- If I can't have it, you can't have it!     - Aah!
- 盖勒教授？ - 路易斯？有什么事吗？
- Professor Geller?     - Yes, Mr. Lewis? How can I help you?
我知道我的期中考没有考好
I know I didn't do well on my midterms and stuff...
但我希望你能帮我改成绩
...but I was kind of hoping you could change my grade.
我为什么要那么做？
And why exactly would I do that?
因为我爱上你了
Because I'm in love with you.
什么？
What?
对 我爱上你了
Yeah. I'm all in love with you and stuff.
- 你可以帮我改成绩吗？ - 不行
- So could you change my grade?     - No!
为什么？你帮奈德改成绩
Well, why not? You changed Ned's grade.
那不一样 因为他真的爱上我了
Well, that's different, okay? Because he was actually in love with me.
不 他才没有 他只是在耍你
No, he's not! He's totally yanking your chain.
他已经用这一招对付过其他三个教授
He's done this with three other teachers.
- 什么？ - 他有女朋友
- What?     - He's got a girlfriend.
我不敢相信有人会为了成绩那么做
I can't believe someone would do that for a grade.
我知道
I know.
那太可怕了
It's awful.
我爱你
I love you.
- 你看到钱德了吗？ - 没有 干嘛？
- Have you seen Chandler?     - No, why?
因为我一直在想 我会失去的一切
I just keep thinking about all these things I'm not gonna have...
我真的吓坏了 我不知道该怎么办
...and it's freaking me out. I don't know what to do about it.
别担心
Okay. Don't sweat it.
钱德不在 别管那么多规矩 那个男的很帅
Chandler is nowhere around, so get it out of your system. That guy's cute.
菲比 别这样 我是认真的
Phoebe, come on, I'm serious.
- 我得跟他谈这件事   - 你真的不该那么做
- I've just gotta talk to him about all this.     - That is the last thing you wanna do.
- 为什么？ - 因为你要嫁给他
- Why?     - Because you're marrying him!
你得说清楚
You gotta help me out here, Pheebs.
我从来没有订婚过 也没有真正结婚过
All right, I've never been engaged and I've never really been married.
我只能告诉你我妈跟我说的话
But I can only tell you what my mother told me.
当你对一段关系有疑虑 害怕或焦虑时…
Whenever you have doubts or fears or anxieties about a relationship...
别跟你的丈夫沟通这些问题
...do not communicate them to your husband.
所以 我不该跟我要共度一生的男人…
So I'm not supposed to share my doubts and fears...
分享我的疑虑跟恐惧？
...with the guy I'm spending the rest of my life with?
没错 就是那样
That is correct. Yes.
你应该把那件事放在心里…
You're supposed to put all that stuff in a little box in your mind...
永远不再提
...and then lock it up tight.
- 那是你妈妈告诉你的？ - 对
- Your mother told you this?     - Yes.
那个结了很多次婚 在你十三岁时就自杀了的女人？
The woman that got married a bunch of times and killed herself when you were 13?
我的天啊 你说的对
Oh, my God, you're right.
去告诉钱德 快点 免得太迟了
All right, go. Go tell Chandler. Hurry, before it's too late!
等一下 这也表示 放荡是得不到真爱的吗？
Wait, no! Does this also mean that putting out doesn't get you love?
(银杯)
- 不敢相信我要跟洁西卡艾许丽碰面   - 等一下
- I can't believe I'm gonna meet Jessica Ashley!     - Wait, wait.
瑞秋 拜托你酷一点 好吗？ 我跟这个女人一起工作
Please be cool, okay? I work with this woman.
- 好吧 我会很酷的   - 好吧
- Okay, I'm totally cool.     - Okay.
请进
Come in.
嘿 洁西卡
Hey, Jessica.
嘿 洁西
Hey, Jess.
她是我朋友瑞秋
This is my friend Rachel.
- 嗨   - 你好吗？
- Hi.     - What's up?
这是你的肥皂奖 我代表你收下了它
Uh, listen, here's your Soapie. I accepted it for you.
我的天啊 我得奖了？ 你知道这代表什么意义吗？
Oh, my God. I won? Do you have any idea what this means?
就这样？ 你不把它摆在柜子里吗？
That's it. You're not gonna put it on your shelf or anything?
不 我只想把真正的奖杯 摆在柜子里 对不起
No, I try to save that for real awards. Now if you'll excuse me?
呵
Hm!
- 要把它拿回去吗？ - 那当然
- Take it back?     - Absolutely.
耶
Yep.
对 做得好
Yeah, you do.
- 甜心？我们快结婚了…   - 哈？
- Honey? As we get closer to the wedding...     - Hm?
有什么事你想跟我分享吗？
...is there anything you'd like to talk about or share?
好吧 我觉得桌上的装饰太大了
Okay. Well, I think the centerpieces are too big.
你错了 桌上的装饰刚刚好
You're wrong. The centerpieces are fine.
- 你曾经觉得害怕过吗？ - 有一点 它们真的很大
- Do you ever get scared at all?     - Kind of. They're really big.
你不害怕自己没办法再认识新的人吗？
Doesn't it ever freak you out that you're never gonna be with anybody new again?
什么？
What?
只是…
Just...
我非常爱你
I love you so much. Just...
有时候我会很难过 我无法再有那样的感觉
It's just sometimes it bothers me that I'm never gonna have that feeling.
当你刚认识一个人…
When you first meet someone for the first time...
你会觉得新鲜刺激 你知道那种心动的感觉吗？
...and it's new and exciting. You know that rush?
不知道
No.
不 当我刚认识一个人…
No, see, when I first meet somebody...
我会觉得慌张 焦虑 满头大汗
...it's mostly panic, anxiety and a great deal of sweating.
好吧 但你是男人
Okay, but... All right, you're a guy.
你不害怕你永远不能 再跟别人上床吗？
Does it not freak you out that you're never gonna sleep with anybody else?
不能跟别人上床
Sleeping with somebody, no.
我害怕的是焦虑 慌张 跟满头大汗
Anxiety, panic and I'm afraid even more sweating.
即使是跟我在一起？
Even with me?
我们刚开始交往的六个月 我严重脱水
I was dangerously dehydrated during the first six months of our relationship.
对我来说心动的感觉是 我们会共度余生
Look, for me the rush is knowing that we are gonna be together for the rest of our lives.
- 真的吗？ - 对
- Really?     - Well, yeah.
知道你有这些想法 我们又回到了慌张 焦虑跟…
Knowing you're having these thoughts, we're back to panic, anxiety and, uh...
我真的需要喝点运动饮料
...I'm definitely gonna need some kind of sports drink.
过来
Come here.
过来 你不必担心
Come here. Oh, sweetie, you don't have to worry.
而且你知道吗？跟你在一起 我一定能遇上新鲜的事
No. Besides, you know what? I'm gonna have a lot of new things with you.
我们第一次买房子 第一个孩子 第一个孙子
The first time we buy a house, our first kid, our first grandkid.
给我水…快点
Water. Water. Water.
摩斯先生？我能跟你谈谈吗？
Uh, Mr. Morse? Can I speak to you for a moment?
你今天上课的内容很精彩
That was a great lecture today.
- 你剪了头发吗？ - 恩
- Did you get a haircut?     - Mm-hm.
对 你喜欢吗？你爱吗？
Yeah, yeah. Do you like it? Do you love it?
我要告诉你我会把你的成绩改回来
I want you to know that I'm changing your grade back.
什么？为什么？
What? Why?
我知道你在搞什么鬼 那是行不通的
Because I know what you're trying to pull here. It's not gonna work.
我没有搞什么鬼 听着 我爱你
I'm not trying to pull anything. Look, I love you, dude.
我甚至不想谈这件事 这个小"风流韵事"结束了
You know what, I'm not even gonna talk about this. This little "thing" is over.
我知道你有女朋友 也知道其他教授的事
I know you have a girlfriend. Yeah. And I know about the other professors.
你觉得那会让我 有什么感觉？你利用我
How do you think that makes me feel, Ned? You used me!
你不爱我 你从来都没有爱过我
You don't love me and you never did!
温斯顿教授 佛迪瑞克森教授
Ah, Professor Winston. Professor Frederickson.
我马上来
I'll be right with you.
别让事情变得更糟糕 我会给你"丙" 我们可以走了吗？
Don't make this worse and I'll give you a C. Shall we?
瑞秋
Rach?
- 我马上来   - 恩
- I'll be out in a second.     - Hm.
"这真的是太意外了
"It's just so unexpected! I...
哈哈
Ha-ha-ha.
我得告诉大家 能被提名诺贝尔奖…
I'll tell you, it's just such an honor to just be nominated...
已经是莫大的光荣
...for a Nobel Prize.
我竟然因为按摩得了诺贝尔奖
And, you know, to win one for a massage! Oh...
特别是我刚拿下 东尼奖的最佳女演员奖…"
Especially after having just won a Tony Award for Best Actress..."
我们订了八点的位置
We have to go. Our reservations are at 8.
"以《我们订了八点的位置》得奖 作词人是尼尔赛门
"...in Reservations at Eight by Neil Simon.
谢谢你 尼尔 谢谢你帮我填词"
Thank you, Neil. Thank you for the words."
好 待会再玩 我们要迟到了
You can finish this later. We're gonna be late. We gotta go.
请不要奏乐 还有一件事
Please don't play the music. Just one more thing.
好吧
Okay.
"纽约现场直播 欢迎收看《周末夜现场》"
"Live from New York, it's Saturday Night!"